Strangers on a Train
Part 1
When the train stopped at the station, I opened my eyes and looked out of the window.
I saw a woman on the platform.
She was tall and blonde with blue eyes.
The train moved and I closed my eyes.
It was 4.00 p.m. and the train was full.
Excuse me. Can I sit here?
I opened my eyes again. It was the tall, blonde woman.
‘Sure,’ I answered.
She sat down next to me. There was a nice smell. Chanel Number 5.
I started to listen to music on my phone.
I love Chopin.
‘Sorry?’ I said.
You’re listening to Chopin. I love classical music.
She smiled. Her eyes were very blue.
We talked about music until the train arrived at Paddington Station.
‘Would you like a cup of coffee?’ she asked me.
I looked at my watch. ‘OK’, I said.
‘I have time.’